<data>
  <id><![CDATA[52289188]]></id>
  <url><![CDATA[https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s?timestamp=1542193931&src=3&ver=1&signature=BCr3pR2wzFii2UXcw1UHedsGIL6x7ietWpgcZKjUh5iuUFABJ6CDMsAsOxfgm5yU96H*WTqn6S2xmqDKLy73Wq4PeZ8cfZKS*QG3xh9JEgrAlMrX0geQKJZ3Kp73d9j6x7kGGSvYS49Wka4VGl0*oLUyWnTNoLEVMk2R3-Nq5lI=]]></url>
  <title><![CDATA[一批又一批的工程师们倒在了苹果公司的面试题前]]></title>
  <content><![CDATA[关注我，你的眼睛会辣来源｜网络编辑｜猿姐你以为从蓝翔毕业就所向无敌啦～nonono～无数老资格的工程师，程序员们纷纷倒在了这些公司的面试题前苹果We have a cup of hot coffee and a small cold milk out of the fridge. The room temperature is in between these two. When should we add milk to coffee to get the coolest combination earliest (at the beginning, in the middle, or at the end)?假设有杯热咖啡和一杯刚从冰箱里拿出来的冰牛奶。室温介于二者之间。问：何时往咖啡里加冰牛奶才能最快得到一杯最凉的咖啡牛奶？（开始、中间、最后）Product Design Engineer产品设计工程师▼What superhero would you be and why?你想成为哪个超级英雄？为什么？Retail零售岗▼Draw the inside architecture of an iPhone画出一台iPhone的内部结构Hardware Test Design硬件测试设计岗▼Give me 5 ways of measuring how much gasoline is in a car.告诉我5个测算一辆汽车里有多少汽油的方法。Hardware Engineering硬件工程师岗▼There are three boxes, one contains only apples, one contains only oranges, and one contains both apples and oranges. The boxes have been incorrectly labeled such that no label identifies the actual contents of the box it labels. Opening just one box, and without looking in the box, you take out one piece of fruit. By looking at the fruit, how can you immediately label all of the boxes correctly?有三个箱子。一个里面全部是苹果，一个里面全部是橘子，还有一个苹果和橘子都有。这三个箱子都贴错了标签，没法从标签上知道里面的内容物。你只可以打开一个箱子，不可以往里头看，拿出一个水果。看着这个拿出来的水果，你如何立即把箱子和正确的标签对应起来？Software QA Engineer软件测试工程师岗亚马逊Amazon is a peculiar company. What is peculiar about you?亚马逊是一家不寻常的公司。你有什么不寻常之处吗？Area manager区域经理岗▼If you had 5,623 participants in a tournament, how many games would need to be played to determine the winner?如果一场锦标赛有5623名参赛者，你认为需要多少局比赛才能决定出胜者？Area manager区域经理岗▼If you saw someone steal a quarter, would you report it?如果你看到有人偷了25美分，你会举报吗？Shipping manifest clerk装运清单专员岗▼Tell me about a time you had to overstep management to get your point of view across.说说你某一次需要越过管理层去传递自己观点的情况。Project manager项目经理岗▼Tell me about a time you solved a complex situation with a simple solution.说说你某一次用很简单的办法解决了很困难的问题的情况。Senior investigation specialist高级调查专员岗微软Why would you not join Google?你为什么不去隔壁谷歌？Senior Business Development Manager高级商务发展经理岗▼How would you determine if a deck of cards is well or poorly shuffled?你如何判断一副扑克牌是否充分地被洗牌？Software Development Engineer软件开发工程师岗▼What did you think about Microsoft's decision to launch Office products on the iPhone?你对微软决定在iPhone上发布Office产品有什么看法？Senior Business Planner高级商务规划岗▼The infamous "clock hands" question -how many times do the hour and minute hands of a clock overlap in a 24 hour period?最讨厌的“钟表指针”问题——在24小时内，时针会和分针重合多少次？Software Development Engineer软件开发工程师岗▼Explain recursion to a 5-year-old kid.把我当五岁小孩，给我解释一下“递归”的概念。Software Engineer软件工程师岗谷歌What is your favorite Google product, and how would you improve it?你最喜欢的谷歌产品是哪个？你打算怎么优化它？Associate product manager产品经理副职岗▼If ads were removed from YouTube, how would you monetize it?如果Youtube去除了广告，你打算用什么方式来赚钱？Associate account strategist会计战略副职岗▼A coin was flipped 1,000 times and there were 560 heads. Do you think the coin is biased?一枚硬币被抛了1000次，共有560次正面。你认为这枚硬币是否有倾向性？Quantitative analyst量化分析师岗▼Estimate the number of tennis balls that can fit into a plane.估算一下一架飞机中可以装下多少个网球？Intern实习生岗相比之下以下这几家公司就有点弱了宝洁Can you tell me a time when you've overcome a problem in a professional environment to reach success?你有没有在专业环境中为获得成功而克服困难的情况，试举一例。▼Describe a situation in which you were able to use persuasion to successfully convince someone to see things your way.你是否曾成功运用说服能力让他人接受你的观点，试举一例。阿迪达斯How do you handle situations that could cause you to be late or miss work?你如何处理会让你迟到或者旷工的情况？▼Describe to me your ideal employer.描述一下你理想中的老板。▼What type of work environment do you dislike working in?你不喜欢在哪种工作环境中工作？腾讯为什么想在这儿工作？软件工程师岗▼你喜欢打什么游戏？软件工程师岗▼为什么选择腾讯？市场营销岗▼你最喜欢的腾讯应用是什么？法务助理岗▼你认为有哪些垂类是腾讯需要做的？移动商务发展经理岗牛B程序猿孤独地写程序时，你需要一些陪伴，一些快乐，一些”干“货。扫码关注！]]></content>
  <author><![CDATA[牛B程序猿]]></author>
  <time>2018-11-06 15:30:00</time>
  <account><![CDATA[shopex-salon]]></account>
  <image><![CDATA[https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_gif/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib4Z6qReDVaicaiaMPsgkTruGElIdjBCqMhOVExKX5BiaeQhEaCTHsgUo5pQ/640?wx_fmt=gif|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_gif/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib4CA74vtw9ib2hbGpUf5ga1T6c6HTicmicJLiblBHMBIdhO1FqHRSIo3HCKQ/640?wx_fmt=gif|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib4M3fld3icWHnnBHwDIDxtrfwxGFnH0BKwGkRzFBDlD0FCfyB1ICQTIdQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib4cZp6rInWeBVp5tjnfk8BvsM9nFI7baZ118PQFMudicpuCVrTIMe7qAg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib41rJtX9j7tBib7ogBn4MicNz44d0afrLh4m4Jn7bHmCPYTRYic7huey1gQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib4ebIIX7MciaYRU7WDFTGL6ffctNRQmZr7gxWVxSO7wOZn0yOeEhj7Kpg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib4cVVibf5fjOZF9e5tibX8BguiapDjXPRXL1l9zgOMf0CbgLMzicmOMxSgbA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib4F4qukf5vdtaZB2rtzGJZEWFaJkZWNjKvBJrpia1j6ZVfhwxp5TuXZsg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib4zrx4k74cop8Kv7gSd91RHDaGCnEKQmvicNXnicFgUn943icQhFUMh0rbQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib4Ds2YJulvC1LX5a3rxQ9icFnDOqqW0gfB146ZldnjicuNmoEZ4BSk4y7w/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib4ZI7DULAnIoVr7IDm9kSDrnibwaDDlVWTZ75FMibBicba4tiaYEkFlDnRdg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/uAw85GfTXziaFyDickAcxzgpeoHoAAMhib46f7SSHcUHicvVy6aGBfHh1C0ZT4LPYWZQtR2ZXWEnym1A20ZyTqU7mA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg]]></image>
</data>
