<data>
  <id><![CDATA[52230211]]></id>
  <url><![CDATA[https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s?timestamp=1542186349&src=3&ver=1&signature=ZlB-2EJfC3xpCH9bC0jMaBb5HZyW0dYFEw5aAiYLf4YcMLli1xOrZRSmhNHMBRKKr3ndBxkA2m0PQP3w8yYsGbr-WXD0*WFzRfiDr9zwofvC*hKWh25n6KwdkHe9YrbUbVGc3OU02y7rBQ3kSZ278xygM4*OmpC*Pfc2I1*gjLg=]]></url>
  <title><![CDATA[2020年迪拜世博会——德国馆，浮动型的屋顶设计！！]]></title>
  <content><![CDATA[柏林建筑事务所（LAVA）将担任2020迪拜世博会展馆的规划设计者。该展馆设计为一个融合了自然和科技的垂直校园，它借鉴了当地建筑风格和德国轻型展馆设计的历史。在形式上，该设计采用浮动型屋顶，其中包含相互连接的浮动立方体，可容纳展览和活动空间。The Laboratory for Visionary Architecture (LAVA) has been selected to design the German Pavilion for Expo 2020 Dubai. Designed as a vertical campus that blends nature and technology, the pavilion takes cues from local architecture and Germany’s history of outstanding lightweight pavilion design. Formally, the design features a freeform roof that encloses interlinked floating cubes that house exhibition and event spaces.展示世博会的主题，从智能利用当地气候条件到材料的再利用和建筑的设计都是可持续的。这个概念延续了德国在世博会展馆设计中的创新，采用了新的空间形成方式- 从1929年Mies van der Rohe的巴塞罗那到1967年Frei Otto的蒙特利尔再到1970年Fritz Bornemann的大阪球形音乐厅。它还回应当地的气候，并参考了当地四合院封闭的外立面和面向内部空间的房间。Demonstrating the Expo theme, everything from intelligent use of local climatic conditions to materials reuse and construction is designed to be sustainable. The concept continues German innovation in Expo pavilion design by using new ways of forming space – from Mies van der Rohe’s Barcelona 1929 to Frei Otto’s Montreal 1967 to Fritz Bornemann’s spherical concert hall Osaka 1970. It also responds to the local climate and references the local courtyard house with closed exterior facade and rooms oriented towards an inner airspace.通风建筑是一个有效堆叠空间体量。封闭空间与身临其境展览体验的对比，在内外部空间之间产生了令人兴奋的交流。开放式结构由抽象元素和令人惊讶的材料组成，是重复和分化的组合。不透明的梯形单层ETFE膜以最小的包覆表面和高效的材料创造了大量的空间。金属表皮通过许多小开口让光线进入室内，类似于阳光穿透森林树叶，创造了不断变化的游客体验。云景屋顶由垂直钢缆支撑，可以阻挡热量，控制中庭的光线和温度。它减少了生产能源，通过减轻重量来优化资源，并为愉快的游客体验创造了技术条件。The airy construction is an efficiently stacked volume of space. The contrast of enclosed air space and immersive exhibition experiences generates an exciting exchange between interior and exterior spaces. The open structure is formed from abstract elements and surprising materials, a composition of repetition and differentiation. An opaque trapezoidal single-layer ETFE membrane creates a large volume of space with a minimal enveloping surface and highly efficient material. The metallic skin lets light rays into the interior through many small openings, similar to sunlight penetrating forest foliage, creating a continuously changing visitor experience. Supported by vertical steel cables, the cloudscape roof keeps out the heat and controls light and temperature in the atrium. It reduces production energy, optimizes resources by weight savings and creates the technical conditions for a pleasant visitor experience.中央中庭，绿色开放空间，连接所有游客区域，并提供许多意外的视野。展览空间，活动区域和餐厅的构成通过这些多种视觉关系交织在一起。展馆之旅将游客不断带到开放式中庭的露台上，提供他们在展馆内的位置、各种主题以及与其他游客的社会互动的概览。德国本土植物悬挂在露台和屋顶上，营造出舒适的中庭和特殊的光线。A central atrium, a green, open space, connects all visitor areas and allows many surprising perspectives. The composition of exhibition spaces, event area and restaurants are interwoven through these manifold visual relationships. The pavilion tour brings visitors continuously onto the terraces of the open atrium, providing an overview of their location within the pavilion, the variety of topics and social interaction with other visitors. Native German plants hang from the terraces and roof creating comfort in the atrium and special light.垂直校园位于较低两层的景观层与云屋顶之间。后方东侧是一个垂直的主体，具有技术设施和服务功能，前面的西侧设有展览和餐厅空。堆叠看似漂浮的建筑元素的序列是一个通过校园学习体验的旅程 - 从入学到学习课程再到毕业。 “实验室”是专为展览，表演和餐饮而设计的，分布在中庭周围。The vertical campus courses between a landscaped layer on the lower two levels and the cloud roof. The rear east is a vertical backbone with technical facilities and service functions, and the front western side houses exhibition and restaurant spaces layered horizontally. The sequence of stacked seemingly floating building elements is a journey through the campus learning experience – from enrollment to learning curriculum to graduation. The ‘laboratories’, purpose designed for exhibition, performance and dining, are grouped around the atrium.2020年世博会的主题是“沟通思想，创造未来”，将于2020年10月20日至2021年4月10日举行。The Expo 2020 theme is "Connecting Minds, Creating the Future" and it runs from 20 October 2020 to 10 April 2021.设计方案气候体量堆叠--示意图剖面图示意图分析图草图建筑师：柏林建筑事务所（LAVA）地点：迪拜合作、宣传、投稿请加小编微信：soujianzhu2关注微信公众号“搜建筑”或微信号“sjz9999”后，回复对应的数字或关键词，查看精品内容！！2018年全新回复：万科回复：1101或 1102 1103 1104 1105 1106 1110龙湖回复：1301或1302 1303恒大回复：1201规范回复：0901车库回复：1001或 1002高层办公回复：0101 或 0102 0103 0104 0106多层办公回复：0201 或 0202 0203 0204 0205综合体回复：0301 或 0302 0303 0304 0305 0307酒店回复：0401 或 0402 0403 0404 0405学校回复：0501 或 0502 0503 0504 05050507售楼处回复：0601或 0602博物文化展览馆回复：0701或 0702 0703 0704  0707图书馆回复：0801或 0802每周户型回复：0001或 0002 0003 0004 0005 0006]]></content>
  <author><![CDATA[搜建筑]]></author>
  <time>2018-11-10 13:32:00</time>
  <account><![CDATA[sjz9999]]></account>
  <image><![CDATA[https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9tFdb3ibm5IqqtgDVAgLZDBqQHHibdrSfOpcd5VHTOcvYceykOpucHwoA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9bajKzkBqN2VYDmuwZDu6micY3wm0sXZM7FovRVib7ZZU5ohb1wiayZnCQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9P36DyxGBFxWcFMnuoEuMHmuDYeYTK55LLI6Ok7GbVqw7Oyhlnuic2QQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9UxIttoGcibacjYTzqfzBCrbJTb6fHIgOTBLc78DHzUWtSGSzR2P0HWQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9wSdOAibpPiaSiaGrdfwiaicbaw1BicDXo0SN4OibqGxYVuA0qficmlibiap39xjA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj97sgtPXYBlr5BQuu2mnIpK21OwGrpZZCv9G2wCDEpg4oNDV5DkWVUYw/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9aO61Tj0naDYZR2tfO2mdNe7y0PZa9a53Xoyic4rTkbfwSgNNVNuKBfA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9WcCVCNbCb5INIswDmlL0xvMH1afsq5Toia7icpkyc3D6AZCVO5EqPS9A/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9c32m9xqBZqN3GputQGfO1CjT7Vu5rtDxax8GhAaKSial4VUfHBO6iazA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9b0Q5hd9d4579wjhjG9UTibYkwfVs5EJP35Tnksc5ZcnvEbbumNSqWTg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9HNnfpTMia3SpoibqptlryPBJJb3h8DicDy6fMKojqfWib7KlAkjn9VLTqg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9D1tGibKJ0gjgODlMmcoY8I9icWRy5yVuPQIV3sqMA2OMVBssv3BoInQw/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9EBNqlxprd4I0N1qaVtPOJVUgmuKey27V95ISOxrePED1ZEBqZFYqcw/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9FV6K5ddDVsT7Otic04iazAHqwVV9PdmXXFg8Khz0M2V1RxIw3lM9SwicQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj9ttKeKLrJYk7k26ktk7JMibXJOB3wjD79J41Tmt8Eezjia6tYT69gx9jA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicMOjns0XDIiaCR4pMZGHXpj92biakhdiaCjYTVX0HAG3ka49ia2x4xZM5d9a3d9NNfN8KfeK3Ka9nRTJA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz/WBjQOjYicFicM1gdTozKXoj405DACCh8INXI7fBks5ykjAnwkqCTOBZKQqbR4YjqHpyTGLOMnL4Tvg0EicIUlkiaRw/640?wx_fmt=gif]]></image>
</data>
