<data>
  <id><![CDATA[52230211]]></id>
  <url><![CDATA[https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s?timestamp=1542186349&src=3&ver=1&signature=ZlB-2EJfC3xpCH9bC0jMaBb5HZyW0dYFEw5aAiYLf4YcMLli1xOrZRSmhNHMBRKKr3ndBxkA2m0PQP3w8yYsGYTFyT5ngJzY5IiM1nKVgDwRpICfUjgFt5fCF8oRFa-zDiU7kWYNl9paI53GV5TrO9Aq2ciZJ4m0w7WfSHKRErs=]]></url>
  <title><![CDATA[世界上第一个水泥打印机，能够在24小时内，完成650平方英尺的住宅。]]></title>
  <content><![CDATA[编者注：本文最初发表于2018年3月27日。最近有消息称，负责该项目的建筑公司ICON已成功为该项目筹集了900万美元的资金。下面是这个项目的一个新视频。Editor's Note: This story was originally published 27 March 2018. It was recently announced that ICON, the construction company leading the project, has successfully raised $9 million in seed funding for the project. A new video of the project is included below.对于那些发达经济体，科技很大程度是为了攫取更多金钱而服务。而对于发展中国家而言，这些科技往往需要经过好几个周期后，才能到达第三世界。这种现象就是所谓的“滴流效应”。Tech gets a bad rap for serving developed economies in the interest of money-making. It often takes a few cycles for the technologies that are truly helpful to reach the developing world, hence the unfortunate, slow-draining term called the “trickle effect.”德克萨斯州奥斯汀的建筑公司ICON和一家致力于解决住房问题的非盈利机构NewStory联手推出了一款3D打印机，只需4000美元就可以建造成品房。这台名为Vulcan的打印机能够在12-24小时内用水泥打印650平方英尺的单层住宅。也许作为寻求新方向的一小步，他们将把打印机转移到拉丁美洲，计划明年之前在萨尔瓦多创建世界上第一个3D打印社区。ICON, a construction company in Austin, Texas, and New Story, a non-profit focusing on housing, have come up with a 3D printer that can build move-in-ready houses for just $4000. The printer, called the Vulcan, is capable of printing a 650sqft, single-story home out of cement in 12-24 hours. And perhaps as a small way to upturn the trajectory of innovation, they are going to move the printer to Latin America, to create the world's first 3D printed community in El Salvador by next year.ICON首席执行官Jason Ballard表示：“我们在ICON的任务是重新设想住宅建筑和建筑的方式，并为全世界的每个人提供经济适用房。” “我们正处于全球房地产危机的中期，让旧的方法变得更好一点并不能解决问题。”“It’s our mission at ICON to re-imagine the approach to homebuilding and construction and make affordable, dignified housing available to everyone throughout the world,” stated Jason Ballard, CEO of ICON. “We’re in the middle of a global housing crisis, and making old approaches a little better is not solving the problem.”这台打印机所打印出的一套成品房目前位于得克萨斯州奥斯汀市。房子设有客厅，卧室，浴室和弧形门廊。它在本月早些时候的2018年SXSW会议上公布。The proof-of-concept home currently sits in Austin, Texas. The house has a living room, bedroom, bathroom, and a curved porch. It was unveiled during the SXSW Conference 2018 earlier this month.打印机主要用的材料是波特兰水泥。住宅建造按照国际建筑规范(IBC)的结构规范标准来进行,预计它们的寿命将等于甚至长于标准混凝土砌块(CMU)建成的住宅。虽然他们现在只打算建造800平方英尺的房屋，但打印机是设置在多轨道的轴上的，所以理论上它具有无限的打印区域。The main material used is Portland cement. These homes are expected to last as long or longer than standard Concrete Masonry Unit (CMU) built homes, and are built to International Building Code (IBC) structural code standards. And although they are only planning to build up to 800 square foot homes for now, the printer is set on tracks on an axis, so it theoretically has an unlimited print area.因为这两家公司相信这些3D打印的房屋可以为住房困难的地区做出巨大的贡献，所以他们选择搬到萨尔多瓦。他们还开始了募款活动，让捐助者可以为一个家庭资助一套3D住宅。The companies are choosing to move to El Salvador because they believe these 3D printed homes can be a powerful contribution to a region that is hard-pressed for shelter. They have also started fundraising campaigns so that donors can fund a 3D home for a family.在拉丁美洲，有3300万人生活在贫民窟中，大多数区域，并不存在“收容所”和类似的服务。 此外，人工建造的同类房屋需要13至20天才能完工，由于劳力和时间的原因，可能成本会更高。希望通过打印机Vulcan，用户现在可以通过简单的下载和打印操作，一天内就搬进新房，并能在其中生活好几个世代。In Latin America, 33 million people live in slums, and “homeless shelters” and similar services do not exist for the most part. Furthermore, human-built equivalent houses take between 13 to 20 days to complete and can cost way more due to labor and time. Hopefully, with the Vulcan, users can now download, print, and move into a new house in a day, and live in it for generations to come.平面图东立面西立面南立面北立面剖面图建筑师：ICON合作、宣传、投稿请加小编微信：soujianzhu2关注微信公众号“搜建筑”或微信号“sjz9999”后，回复对应的数字或关键词，查看精品内容！！2018年全新回复：万科回复：1101或 1102 1103 1104 1105 1106 1110龙湖回复：1301或1302 1303恒大回复：1201规范回复：0901车库回复：1001或 1002高层办公回复：0101 或 0102 0103 0104 0106多层办公回复：0201 或 0202 0203 0204 0205综合体回复：0301 或 0302 0303 0304 0305 0307酒店回复：0401 或 0402 0403 0404 0405学校回复：0501 或 0502 0503 0504 05050507售楼处回复：0601或 0602博物文化展览馆回复：0701或 0702 0703 0704  0707图书馆回复：0801或 0802每周户型回复：0001或 0002 0003 0004 0005 0006]]></content>
  <author><![CDATA[搜建筑]]></author>
  <time>2018-11-14 13:32:00</time>
  <account><![CDATA[sjz9999]]></account>
  <image><![CDATA[https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrBLbWYCJX7beIM8cuZWdKNOq3cqJslLbnlRQxHyjUwBQyneeRHZWMyQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0Jyr7IwPRQz05xUyqFkKArnRNsyQv3Poy8691ibGicwIE4l1jzj5RRDo5pNg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0Jyr4SnBmXxn7p6ugicA6dkSK6xEeZ6v8xCFiaAoL6mD5NjjMvAsmQfPltiaw/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrSTcsZjW5yOaian4A3IF5WMnN5AibPzCrnVaFKxCYwkDI3U1VAibawwRicw/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrOxCwo4rJ5tfrx1EUYX3wOc0yPXMBxrLibL8XOb5C8moKmQ1URN3GtwA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrxZKS8Fav2RO1pTfrH25iaBYgiaocTzXuNC67ZA8EBQw2tzesVWkUDHMQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrYMoqLgicXzTcDFiaozTzGicKK9QptzzGBYUQEAs8Ztw3NHNKGTO8PZibtQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrVQwugVEic1kToWZXfespoTjC6tmNvWExfLQMOmZu23OaJcfjFfSh5bQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrK9C0dvMcPSW4IFyVVtJgsogibbzKG1CUXX2p9l8LctaGn7WxKB1icqEA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyryRtCBhebE1lwqHOOYPAhaV0blToojwJhKfKc44noPKQurqiaDiahTlmA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrEic2eiafj1SpQQbKRAzRvXzBpyNUf5dzLZoJo9kCQ1VjV0S9uJoc4Lgw/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrJmU2qjs5ic0yOicrshusINeWISvjUF3ALvr5eK4D52BfK9eu1AgXiaw6g/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrVJN3Jx9tktVjL2jmqaEmwQ3jkZ5Fl0tToPXhnJspTDxhvOMhpno3cg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrwNos2yJWqTPL1k14W4As4zZicxWyVbia7Wa39OSZ0JYPibKden9nibJ7xQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0Jyr44iayWF88sp7jy1TGJRHao4GDsrY6SUQvIp4aNIREjvFrmJibdrwEykg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrPDWfNMnF2Zx8ZUf0JkfqKF9sDCibNBEMAmKyleCIDTB8Yib2gvNEZDiaQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0Jyr62BBQibu4iaAfzibiamsSjiaYQhA67NJibZvs9fafUZ7LBqicrna8TFcop7GA/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrMbj405qGVGdibnDTqGQDmkwQR9f7GUmyOvTpCNk4HLjMxkGqR7hzWbg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrQxib3Ra4L1UM0K0Hj7H5RFJPQ4icnQCd40gxMv5icEKESvDuIA4fsRicSQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrwfInzqfVL4WibaNWqAN63vXcAUgvaBcrYRSk83CrvyeItFOsMOZI8zQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0Jyr2wMK0hxAo5U0hF1eUeGvRHqPLBUdBwibEopH1e6wnYjVYNHGNkVz30g/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0Jyr2zLhtFsTkxs0PQBwOGG7Uq5y373jwHaToAdibvZgyn0xDD3WvoicDxUQ/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0Jyr8ibNt1Hej1jwicGHTgICD1333N0G7YmnBWLG4qzIDbokT5Yuz3RqhpUw/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0Jyr2UMrsWPDa021y4zcIMn6dzhbmBENvog3iaMrx8EDtX7qJfpzI5XLQxg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrRBC9jBMp67cPicm1LQk8XBX5SA4iaiaBDNCGibImS4rvUBjAbNWc2cbZgg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz/WBjQOjYicFicM1gdTozKXoj405DACCh8INXI7fBks5ykjAnwkqCTOBZKQqbR4YjqHpyTGLOMnL4Tvg0EicIUlkiaRw/640?wx_fmt=gif]]></image>
</data>
