<data>
  <id><![CDATA[52230211]]></id>
  <url><![CDATA[https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s?timestamp=1542186349&src=3&ver=1&signature=ZlB-2EJfC3xpCH9bC0jMaBb5HZyW0dYFEw5aAiYLf4YcMLli1xOrZRSmhNHMBRKKr3ndBxkA2m0PQP3w8yYsGYTFyT5ngJzY5IiM1nKVgDxhPYVXeGnHMUYuqOUnmBvOf2XocSTgrBJqnTyj3o4m7eSGntlYDHFpTV4w7-xY-9I=]]></url>
  <title><![CDATA[MVRDV的获奖作品：一个新的、大胆的红砖综合体！！]]></title>
  <content><![CDATA[由荷兰工作室MVRDV设计的获奖作品RED7综合体在莫斯科正式推出。该公司在俄罗斯的第一座建筑开始于其289套公寓的销售和新发布的提案图像。该公司受该地区革命后，构建主义建筑的影响 - 即邻近的alexey shchusev设计的narkomzem，现在是展示红砖砌体的“农业部”。在天际线上方七十八米处，通往莫斯科市中心的地标门户将为这座城市带来一个大胆的新形象。the winning competition entry RED7 by dutch studio MVRDV has officially been launched in moscow. the firm’s first building in russia commences with sales of its 289 apartments and new released imagery of the proposal. the firm was influenced by the area’s post-revolutionary, socially oriented constructivist buildings of the area — namely, the adjacent alexey shchusev-designed narkomzem, now the ‘ministry of agriculture’ which showcases red brick masonry. rising seventy-eight meters over the skyline, the new symbolic gateway into the center of moscow will offer a bold new character to the city.MVRDV的RED7，之前名为'the silhouette'，将包括豪华公寓，体育中心，灵活的工作空间，活动空间和空中甲板。这座建筑的顶层有着不同配置与大小的公寓，最大的一座能够提供四面八方的俯瞰景观。与此同时，地下项目包括一个超级市场以及商业住宅两用的公园设施。超过60％的公寓享有城市的绝佳景致，超过20％的公寓使用外部露台充分利用其位置。RED7 by MVRDV, previously entitled ‘the silhouette,’ will comprise luxury apartments, a sports center, flexible workspace, an event space, and a sky deck. the building’s top floors accommodate apartments in a variety of configurations and sizes, with the largest providing panoramic views in every direction. underground programs include a supermarket and both commercial and residential parking. over 60% of the apartments have commanding views over the city, and over 20% make the most of their position with external terraces.该建筑的外部将采用特别定制的红砖完成，不仅参考了附近的构建主义建筑，而且还确保实现了一个温暖而受欢迎的住宅区。室内设计将由各种室内设计师完成，包括两个荷兰公司：sabine marcelis和i29，以及俄罗斯oleg klodt。虽然MVRDV在2017年12月赢得了为业主GK osnova设计RED7竞赛，但该建筑将于本月底开始施工，预计将于2022年完工。the building’s exterior will be finished in specially customized red bricks, a reference to the nearby constructivist heritage and an emphasis on the warm and welcoming nature of the project. the interiors will be completed by a variety of interior designers, including two dutch offices, sabine marcelis and i29 interior architects, and a russian office, oleg klodt. while MVRDV won the competition to design RED7 for client GK osnova in december 2017, construction on the building will begin at the end of this month, with completion projected for 2022.建筑师：MVRDV地点：莫斯科面积：52,000平方米混合综合体，28,320平方米住宅、8,230平方米商业用地、1,375平方米共享设施以及13,310的地下停车场合作、宣传、投稿请加小编微信：soujianzhu2关注微信公众号“搜建筑”或微信号“sjz9999”后，回复对应的数字或关键词，查看精品内容！！2018年全新回复：万科回复：1101或 1102 1103 1104 1105 1106 1110龙湖回复：1301或1302 1303恒大回复：1201规范回复：0901车库回复：1001或 1002高层办公回复：0101 或 0102 0103 0104 0106多层办公回复：0201 或 0202 0203 0204 0205综合体回复：0301 或 0302 0303 0304 0305 0307酒店回复：0401 或 0402 0403 0404 0405学校回复：0501 或 0502 0503 0504 05050507售楼处回复：0601或 0602博物文化展览馆回复：0701或 0702 0703 0704  0707图书馆回复：0801或 0802每周户型回复：0001或 0002 0003 0004 0005 0006]]></content>
  <author><![CDATA[搜建筑]]></author>
  <time>2018-11-14 13:32:00</time>
  <account><![CDATA[sjz9999]]></account>
  <image><![CDATA[https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_png/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrmocVUL7wlrXXP1mzuhtkfEhF5uzunGibFaibBmwzllr0LuhGrhiap73Hw/640?wx_fmt=png|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_png/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrCmooQ8gUic0PnOCeHxtEMNibCcH6Wc6Hy9icpVPH3d89AaP0WzgLDbZyw/640?wx_fmt=png|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_jpg/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrsYatZykGEe8eTmibuePbePvpEx0UAgVFDqDhMiccUU4pQYqz5qakniaMg/640?wx_fmt=jpeg|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_png/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrNywFvKIOROMfL3iaiaT41ib12librHO7bpfsUNHAx1bMpNa0FliaJ7xWxag/640?wx_fmt=png|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_png/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrYSGDsZQicFkibaFnlbSaiaYxHwhvzrPm3MibiaqYthly7I4UHmxg6Fa63kA/640?wx_fmt=png|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_png/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrP5BjmeUhrF16KiakEzL0AQESC5ictQI84Dex7QIu8SAg6dS49fNdMmIg/640?wx_fmt=png|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_png/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0Jyrbgp3605RLx9vPxe4Up1C11UaXPzw7Zko1yWIeUv94yDhuUwTBD1N9w/640?wx_fmt=png|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz_png/WBjQOjYicFicOWouxO5zia8VMIGrILm0JyrAQib3Jxw5NbsMXwib0xRvkjT3bOYZGJPeiboG0TsnuOibvgvWbUY67ao9A/640?wx_fmt=png|https://mmbiz.qpic.cn/mmbiz/WBjQOjYicFicM1gdTozKXoj405DACCh8INXI7fBks5ykjAnwkqCTOBZKQqbR4YjqHpyTGLOMnL4Tvg0EicIUlkiaRw/640?wx_fmt=gif]]></image>
</data>
